Where has this manager sir gone missing? Did you
get any information?
Look, we have found out that his last known location was
in Beur.  He said
that I had met with an accident and was
in a serious condition.  But the arrival of anyone like this
in any private hospital nearby, or
in any private hospital across Patna, has
not been confirmed yet.
Neither PMCH nor NMCH has been able to do this
in any government hospital.
We knew there were CCTV cameras around there or through
other technical means that he was talking to someone.
We are collecting information about where he was in contact and till what time his mobile was on.
We are in talks with the family members as well as their
friends.  If he had
any family tension or there was some other apprehension
that he might go there or the
police is investigating all the points.  Hopefully,
we will recover him very soon.
Well, the place where this party was taking place was
Ramakrishna Nagar area and the last location
detail was found towards the jail.
That border was of Kankar Bagh.  Investigation is going on on that matter.
Why have you gone there?  If there is
any movement in their bank account
or we get any kind of information.
His last location was told to
you that he was seen going towards the
plum on his own.  Since then we have
not been able to get any further confirmation.   He was
seen walking on a scooter.
FIR has been registered in Kankar Bagh police station,
right?
Yes, FIR 6425 has been registered.
Police are investigating further.  Hopefully, there will be some confirmation on this very soon.
See, the branch manager of ICICI is Abhishek Varun.
He has gone missing.  The family members
are very worried.  The family members are present at Kankra Bagh police station at this time.
FIR has also been registered.
Police is busy investigating.  His brother is
with us.  Abhishek is Varun ji's brother.   Yes
sir.
What is your name?
Yogesh Varun.
Well, how did something happen?
These people had gone there for a function just yesterday.   The
name is in Krishna Nagar area.
No, this has become Bigpur area.
Yes.
So it was our marriage anniversary there.  His
friend's parents
left from there at night and could not be traced in the morning.
You guys went out and investigated, went to the place where the party was,
searched the hospitals there, went to the nearby areas,
we investigated everywhere, Sir, what happened,
and sent the wife and child home
and told them that we will come and then suddenly in the night he
called and said what should he say that I have met with an
accident,
yes what should he
say on the phone at night, he
called his wife and said that I have met with an accident, I have hurt my
waist, I am not able to get up,
ok then
take me from here,
after that his phone got switched off,
no it is on, it rang till 11:00 in the morning
but after that
it is switched off.  F
is now F switched off.
Meaning, he went to a party at a place with his wife and children.   I
sent my children and wife home and told them
that I will be back soon and at 3:00 pm I called and
said that I had met with an accident.
After that the phone got switched off again and you people are
searching for it but the search is continuing
but it is not being found.   Ca
n't find it.
What do you feel?
So it will happen only after meeting sir.  As
time passes, it is a matter of concern.  It increases.
Law and order has also deteriorated
in Bihar as major incidents are happening one after the other.
This matter came to light at such a time but he
himself is calling and informing that I had an
accident.  Then the phone got switched off.  We talked last
night also.
Yes, he has
also been talked to on 112.   If you
talked to the police, are you saying anything
?
So it seems that the police are also trying their best.
Or are you suspecting something else?
So no doubt.   So it's
not like there was a fight going on in the family.   Have you
gone somewhere yourself?   No. No.  There is no
such thing.  Sir, do
you guys have any doubts about anyone?   There
is no doubt.
What do you want?   I
want him to return home safely as soon as possible.  Everything,
yes sir,
so see, Abhishek Varun had gone to
a function with his family, after that he sent his children and
wife home and said that he would
come soon, then at 3:00 in the night he called and said
that he had met with an accident and since then
his phone is off.  The family members
are very worried.  The police were informed.  An
FIR has been registered at Kankar Bagh police station.  The police are
continuously engaged in the search.  But till now no
information about Abhishek Varun has been found.
Shashank Kumar ABP News Patna with camera person Niranjan.
[music]